<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on GoCV - Golang Computer Vision Using OpenCV 3</title>
    <link>https://gocv.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on GoCV - Golang Computer Vision Using OpenCV 3</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gocv.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Go, OpenCV, Caffe, and Tensorflow: Putting It All Together With GoCV</title>
      <link>https://gocv.io/blog/2018-01-23-go-opencv-tensorflow-caffe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gocv.io/blog/2018-01-23-go-opencv-tensorflow-caffe/</guid>
      <description>We are pleased to present to you the new GoCV (https://gocv.io) version 0.8.0, which is our first release of 2018. This is a big update and adds a lot of powerful new functionality, along with bug fixes and more documentation, thanks to our wonderful contributors.
The new version adds support for the OpenCV Deep Neural Network (DNN) module, which means you can now use Caffe (http://caffe.berkeleyvision.org/) and Tensorflow (https://www.tensorflow.org/) models from your GoCV code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Putting Eyes on the IoT - The Video</title>
      <link>https://gocv.io/blog/2017-12-14-putting-eyes-on-the-iot-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gocv.io/blog/2017-12-14-putting-eyes-on-the-iot-video/</guid>
      <description>The video from &amp;ldquo;Putting Eyes on the IoT: Advanced Computer Vision Using Golang&amp;rdquo;, the talk about GoCV during the Intel Global IoT Devfest, has just been posted online.
Check it at at:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eR8T8rvlNuk
Even if you are a newcomer to Go programming or computer vision, the talk is intended so you can get something useful out of it.
Also, provides useful information about not just OpenCV but also the Intel Computer Vision SDK, which has not had a lot of tutorial content yet overall, let along in Golang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the GoCV Blog</title>
      <link>https://gocv.io/blog/2017-12-14-gocv-the-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gocv.io/blog/2017-12-14-gocv-the-blog/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps you have been wondering &amp;ldquo;where is the blog for this project?&amp;rdquo;. Well, wonder no more, here it is!
We have a Twitter account too We also now have an &amp;ldquo;official&amp;rdquo; Twitter account at @GoCVio please follow us.
What we will cover Updates to GoCV or to OpenCV itself, cool things built with GoCV, events we attend, and the like.
We want to hear from you! Are you using GoCV for something?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>